<?xml version="1.0"?>
<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20140731</CreaDate><CreaTime>14474400</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20160229</ModDate><ModTime>172743</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><toolbox name="RAPID Tools" alias="RAPID Tools"><arcToolboxHelpPath>c:\program files (x86)\arcgis\desktop10.5\Help\gp</arcToolboxHelpPath><toolsets><toolset name="Postprocessing"/><toolset name="Preprocessing"/><toolset name="Utilities"/></toolsets></toolbox><dataIdInfo><idCitation><resTitle>RAPID Tools</resTitle></idCitation><idAbs>Includes seven tools: 1. Create Connectivity File 2. Create Muskingum Parameter Files 3. Create Subset File and 4. Create Weight Table From ECMWF Runoff, 5. Create Inflow File from ECMWF Runoff, 6. Create Weight Table from WRF Geogrid, and 7. Create Inflow File from WRF-Hydro Runoff. Toobox Version 1.0, Updated on Aug 8, 2014. Toolbox Version 2.0, Updated on Oct 24, 2014, deleted the tool of Create Inflow File From ECMWF, and added four tools: Create Weight Table From WRF Geogrid, Create Inflow File From WRF-Hydro Runoff, Create Weight Table From ECMWF Runoff, and Create Inflow File From ECMWF Runoff. Toolbox Version 2.1, Updated on Feb 05, 2015, enhancement in Create Weight Table From WRF Geogrid: modified the equation for calculating central scale factor for MAP_PROJ = 2 according to Kevin Sampson; bug fixings in Create Connectivity File: corrects input parameter indices; Create Inflow File From ECMWF Runoff: calculates RAPID inflow from cumulative runoff, and outputs netCDF3-classic as file format; Create Inflow File From WRF-Hydro Runoff: outputs netCDF3-classic as file format; Create Weight Table From ECMWF Runoff: enables input catchment feature class with spatial reference that is not GCS_WGS_1984; and Create Weight Table From WRF Geogrid: enables output CG Point file name. Toolbox Version 2.2, Updated on Feb 20, 2015, tool redesign in Create Inflow File From ECMWF Runoff, and Create Inflow File From WRF-Hydro Runoff: added an input parameter of drainage line features, and output inflow based on the ascending order of all stream IDs in the drainage line feature class; bug fixings in Create Inflow File From WRF-Hydro Runoff: included UGDRNOFF as a component of stream inflow, and calculated inflow assuming that WRF-Hydro runoff variables are cumulative through time. Toolbox Version 2.3, Updated on Apr 28, 2015, bug fixings in Create Inflow File From WRF-Hydro Runoff and Create Inflow File From ECMWF Runoff: to deal with the first several rows of records in the weight table don't correspond to any drainage line featuresMinimum requirements: ArcGIS 10.2 or later. Toolbox Version 2.3.1, Updated on May 12, 2015, added a new tool Update Weight Table: this tool is temporary and will be merged with Create Weight Table tools later. Updated on May 24, 2015, bug fixing in Update Weight Table: bug fixing: set npoints as 1 in the replacement_row, and fixed the overwritting problem of the replacement_row. Toolbox Version 3.0, Updated on May 29, 2015, added three tools for RAPID postprocessing: Create Discharge Table, Create Discharge Map, and Update Discharge Map; bug fixing in Create Inflow File From ECMWF Runoff and Create Inflow File From WRF-Hydro Runoff: the pointer of weight table goes out of range. Toolbox Version 3.1, Updated on June 2, 2015, bug fixing on Update Discharge Map: symbology didn't get updated if using different classify method. Toolbox Version 3.2, Updated on June 4, 2015, tool enhancement: integrated the updating weight table functionality in both Create Weight Table tools. Toolbox Version 3.2, Updated on June 09, 2015, tool redesign: removed input drainage line feature class and computed RAPID inflow based on the streamIDs in the weight table in both Create Inflow File tools. Toolbox Version 3.2, Updated on July 31, 2015, deprecated the tool of Update Weight Table; added new tools, Copy Data To Server, Publish Discharge Map, and Flowline To Point; categorized tools into three sets, Preprocessing, Postprocessing, and Utilities. Toolbox Version 3.2, Updated on Oct 30, 2015, enhancement in Create Discharge Table: now the tool handles variable/dimension names in no matter uppercase or lowercase, and variable with dimensions in various sequences. Toolbox Version 3.3, Updated on 2/26/2016, fixed bug and removed a redundant loop on Create Weight Table From WRF Geogrid tool; updated on 2/29/2016, used numpy array for faster query in Create NetWork Connecitivity tool.</idAbs><idPurp>includes three toolsets: RAPID preprocessing, postprocessing, and utility tools. The preprocessing tools prepare spatial and temporal inputs data for RAPID. The postprocessing tools create a data model and visualize RAPID output of stream flow over the stream network. Utility tools help automate the process of publishing the stream flow visualization into map service.</idPurp></dataIdInfo><distInfo><distributor><distorFormat><formatName>ArcToolbox Toolbox</formatName></distorFormat></distributor></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"/></mdHrLv></metadata>
